<resources>
    <string name="app_name">City Map</string>


    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string-array name="category_arrays">
        <item>Coffee</item>
        <item>Banks</item>
        <item>Education</item>
        <item>Restaurants</item>
        <item>Pharmacies</item>
        <item>Hotels</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="cafe"><br>Shadërvan\n</br><br>Prizren, 20000</br> </string>
    <string name="marashi"><br>Vatrat Shqiptare 25\n</br><br>Prizren, 20000</br></string>
    <string name="gatsby"><br>Gatsby\n</br><br>Cafe</br> </string>
    <string name="gjimnazi"><br>Gymnasium\n</br><br>Gjon Buzuku</br> </string>
    <string name="gjimnazil">Lekë Matrënga <br>Prizren, 20000 </br> </string>
    <string name="jara"><br>Rruga e Jonit\n</br><br>Prizren, 20000</br> </string>
    <string name="prizren"> Prizren is a city and municipality located in the Prizren District of Kosovo.
        According to the 2011 census, the city of Prizren has 85,119 inhabitants, while the municipality has 177,781 inhabitants.
        Prizren is a historic city located on the banks of the Prizren Bistrica river, and on the slopes of the Šar Mountains
        in the southern part of Kosovo. The municipality has a border with Albania and North Macedonia. </string>

    <string name="marashi1"><br>Vatrat Shqiptare 25-Prizren, 20000\n</br><br>Good restaurant with nice views over the river.</br>
   It\'s placed next to the river and among trees and it has a garden in front as well with beautiful flowers and rich in color. Inside it has a very modern and cozy atmosphere. Just by that it\'s worth a visit. Well worth a visit!</string>
    <string name="gatsby1"><br>Shadërvan Prizren, 20000\n</br><br>Excellent atmosphere, great food and the service is just perfect. Large windows or large openings in the facade, follow natural light, perform two-way ventilation and create a splendid view over the Lumbardh River, the Castle and beyond the fabulous Sharr mountains.Such a kind and pleasant staff. You should definitely try it!</br></string>

    <string name="hotel"><br>Theranda Hotel is located in the center of the ancient city of Prizren\n</br><br>Hotel offers accommodation with elegant rooms, meeting facilities for meetings and workshops and restaurant with terrace surrounded by the most beautiful view of the city. Capacity: Our hotel has 96 rooms in total which of them:Suites (with Jacuzzi), double rooms (with separate beds), double rooms (king size bed), single rooms, triple rooms, rooms for four and five persons .</br></string>

    <string name="banks"><br>Shaip Spahiu, Shadervan\n</br><br>Banka Ekonomike was licensed in 2001 when it also started operating as the only 100 percent local bank.
Being the only fully owned local capital bank, our mission took on an even more important dimension because through providing a higher level service, we would like to give an example that this could also be achieved by an established financial institution entirely from the country.</br></string>

    <string name="gjimnazi2"><br>Lekë Matrënga Prizren, 20000\n</br><br>The school can be separated into three education fields:\n</br><br>General fields\n</br><br>Natural sciences\n</br><br>Mathematics and computing science.</br></string>

    <string name="jara1"><br>Rruga e Jonit Prizren, 20000\n</br><br>Jara Pharmacy is a pharmacy with a new concept of presentation.
Where at first glance, it can be seen that orthopedic and cosmetic products have been given a special and easily accessible space by customers.
The part of pharmaceutical products is located in the part dedicated to them and conforms to pharmaceutical rules.</br> </string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
